

About me

I am a creative and self-taught software developer, based in São José dos Campos, Brazil. I am 23. My career is focused on Web development (Frontend and Backend), I also had experience with Mobile (React Native) and Python development.

Skills

Next JS

React JS

React Native

Javascript

Python

Web Scraping (bs4, Selenium)

Docker

Git

Scrum

Education Background

Universidade Tecnológica Federal do Paraná - BS Software Engineering

Contact information

+55 12 997597922 luisgmfarias@gmail.com



luisgmfarias.github.io



github.com/luisgmfarias



in linkedin.com/in/luisgmfarias

Luís Farias

FRONTEND · PYTHON · WEB CRAWLING

CAREER SUMMARY

Software Engineer - Zenvia

Aug 2022 - present

Angular and Node development for Zenvia Bots and Zenvia Conversion

Fullstack Software Engineer - xnv.io

Sep 2021 - July 2022

Built our React Native mobile MVP project from scratch; Development of our contract flow page with ReactJS and Redux; Developed new features in our Django and DRF backend project.

Software Engineer - Alana.ai

May 2021 - Sep 2021

Built unit tests to our NLP routines; Maintenance of Python API (using FalconAPI).

Jr Data Scientist - Mais Retorno

June 2020 - May 2021

Helped to build our Airflow architecture; Formatting and validated data (Python); Maintenance of our Data Engineering process (Pyspark, SQL, Docker)

Engineering Summer Internship -

Quero Educação

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

Developed a simple internal web application, using ReactJS; Also developed an internal Python webhook API that communicates Slack with GLPI (IT Governance Software).

Research College Visitor - NASA

Goddard Space Flight Center

Jan 2018

Python software to extract a neutral wave activity from the atmosphere from a balloon of the BARREL mission.